Nasser Ali Karimi

Senior Software Engineer with six years experience, specialized in developing PHP and JavaScript Web Applications and Websites for small to large sized businesses around the world.

From: Kabul, Afghanistan Citizenship: Afghan Tel:+93 766 241 789 Email LinkedIn

WORK EXPERIENCE

Get Messiah Pty Ltd, Australia — *Senior Laravel Developer (Nov 2021 - Present)* Messiah is an AdTech platform founded by digital advertisers, for advertisers.

- Developing a Laravel Web Application for Facebook marketing and advertising management
- Integrating third party services like Meta, Stripe, Crisp, Segment and Twilio
- Designing database schema, developing key features and analyzing data
- Participating on UI and UX implementation, API and Webhooks integration
- Get Messiah App (Getmessiah.app)
- Get Messiah Website (Getmessiah.io)

Clik Global (PomTech's partner), Colorado Springs — Senior Software Engineer (Jan 2018 - Nov 2021)

It is a US based company that offers software and web services worldwide.

- Worked on multiple projects, as part of a remote international team
- Delivered and maintained Web Applications and Websites for their American client base
- Technologies used include Drupal, Laravel, WordPress,PHP, JavaScript, Angular, Vue.js, and Bootstrap.
- **AMT** (santarosa.letsdance.tech)
- Adaptive Medical Partners (adaptive medical partners.com)
- AD-ID (ad-id.org)
- Norris Memorial Services (norrismemorialservices.com)
- HCO Store Development (hcowoodworks.net)
- Ratedly (ratedly.com)

Upwork, Remote — *Freelance Software Engineer* (Jan 2018 - Present) Upwork is an American freelancing platform.

- Worked independently on a project basis
- Delivered and maintained existing web applications for international clients.
- Technologies used include Drupal, Laravel, WordPress,PHP, JavaScript and Bootstrap.
- Drupal Full Stack Developer (intrado.com, support.crs.org, driven-am.com)
- PHP Developer (easydoctor.io)
- Drupal Development (socialnicheguru.com)
- WordPress Developer (palsglobal.com, dentist-manila.com)

LANGUAGES

Github

English: Advanced (C1)

Persian: Native

EDUCATION

Kateb University (2016 - 2019) Bachelor in Computer Science

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PHP, JavaScript, Drupal, Laravel, WordPress, Angular, Vue.js, jQuery, CSS, HTML, Git, Bootstrap, REST API, Drush, Python, Django, MySQL, MongoDB, PHPMyAdmin

PLATFORMS & TOOLS

Deployment with AWS, cPanel and Webmin, VSCode, Linux

OTHER SKILLS

Teamwork, code reviewer, project management, database design

AWARDS

Stackoverflow over 4k reputations Certified from JoinImagine

Momtaz Host, Kabul — *Web Developer* (Nov 2015 - Oct 2017) It is a provider of Google Workspace and Gmail server in Afghanistan.

- Worked with a team for Afghan clients
- Designed and developed multiple websites for multiple categories like news, online shop, small to large businesses, universities and health centers.
- Technologies used include WordPress,PHP, JavaScript and Bootstrap.
- Alimi ERP (erp.shaiqalimi.com)
- Roya Film House (rfh-c.org)
- COST (cost.af)
- Zawul (zawul.edu.af)